sumopandagames.com 2012-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Free Shipping - SHOEBACCA.com

  1. ### Acknowledgement and Acceptance of Terms of Use

SHOEBACCA.com is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing SHOEBACCA.com, you acknowledge and fully understand SHOEBACCA.com’s Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement. SHOEBACCA.com has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy@shoebacca.com](mailto:privacy@shoebacca.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe [here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

  2. ### Information We Collect and How We Use It

SHOEBACCA.com collects certain information from and about its users in three ways: directly from our Web Server logs, our users, and with cookies.

  3. ### Web Server Logs

When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:

    1. Your Internet protocol address.
    2. The kind of browser or computer you use.
    3. Number of links you click within the site.
    4. State or country from which you accessed the site.
    5. Date and time of your visit.
    6. Name of your Internet service provider.
    7. Web page you linked to our site from.
    8. Pages you viewed on the site.
  4. ### Use of Cookies

SHOEBACCA.com may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality. SHOEBACCA.com reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies, but does not allow other companies to place cookies on our website unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value (such as merging into SHOEBACCA.com a site that relies on third-party cookies). You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.

  5. ### Personal Information Users

Visitors to our website can register an account with SHOEBACCA.com. When you register, we will request some personal information such as name, address, email, telephone number, account number and other relevant information. When making a purchase, we will request payment related information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for your purchase. Your credit card information may be forwarded to your credit card provider when making a purchase. You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be warranted in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting.

We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:

    1. To fulfill your service requests,
    2. To protect ourselves from liability,
    3. To respond to legal process or comply with law, or
    4. In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.
  6. ### Use of Web Beacons or GIF files

SHOEBACCA.com Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons — sometimes also called single-pixel gifs — that allow SHOEBACCA.com to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. SHOEBACCA.com may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to our website and how you use the site. SHOEBACCA.com prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information.

  7. ### Accessing Web Account Information

We will provide you with the means to ensure that personally identifiable information in your web account file is correct and current. You may review this information by contacting us by sending an email to our customer service department.

  8. ### Opt-In - Opt-Out

Unless you have chosen to subscribe to our Newsletter, we will not use your SHOEBACCA.com registration information to send you promotional materials. We do not transfer, sell or release user names, e-mail addresses or registration information to any business partner, advertiser, sponsor, or outside organization. You may opt-out at any time by simply clicking the opt-out link at the bottom of our newsletter or log into My Account, click the newsletter tab and uncheck the newsletter box.

  9. ### Agents/Service Providers

We use other third parties such as a shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services, an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf [a third party marketing provider to provide broadcast email services for us]. We use Live Chat to assist you if you have questions while using our site or regarding your order. When you sign up for our newsletter, we will share information as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

  10. ### Widgets and Social Networking Features

Our Web site includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

  11. ### Blogs/Forums/Product Reviews

If you link to our blog from this Web site, you should be aware that you will be redirected to our additional site, which is not covered under this policy. Please note any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. We also post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.

  12. ### Links to Other Websites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites, such as our channel on YouTube, whose privacy practices may differ from those of SHOEBACCA.com. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

  13. ### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). [To learn more about SSL, follow this [link](https://trustsealinfo.verisign.com/splash?form_file=fdf/splash.fdf&dn=www.shoebacca.com&lang=en).] We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us [customerservice@shoebacca.com](mailto:customerservice@shoebacca.com).

  14. ### Changes to this Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

  15. ### Contacting Us

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us or send your comments to: 

#### SHOEBACCA.com

Attention: Privacy Statement Personal  
2205 East Pioneer Drive  
Irving, TX 75061

EFFECTIVE DATE: 08/05/2010
